没有演示报告我怎么去开那个会?
How am I supposed to walk into that meeting with no presentation?
你们怎么会搞砸的?
How the hell did you screw this up?
不是我
It wasn't me.
- 她在说谎  - 不 我们协商过
- She's lying. - No,we agreed.
财务数据都在她们那儿
Her team had all the financials.
我们为数据建模忙得不可开交 所以才协商由你们做幻灯片
And we were swamped modeling them.That's why we agreed that you would do the slides.
反正是你们中的一个搞砸的 快点找出来是谁
Well,one of you screwed up,so please try to figure it out.
因为当这个客户踢了我时 我需要知道应该炒谁
'Cause when the client dumps me,I  need to know who to fire.
我通过Email确认过 等着
Look,I  confirmed it in an email.Hold on.
这里
Here.
她确实跟你讲过 Russ
She did   tell you about it,russ.
见鬼这是什么? 我没收到过
What the hell?I never got this.
Russ 你还好吧?
Russ,are you okay?
你喝醉了吗?
Are you drunk?
我没有喝醉
I'm not drunk.
我不知道他又开始喝酒了
I had no idea he was drinking again.
你应该知道
Well,you should have.
给我五分钟 我去商务中心把图表 直接从数据表里打出来
Give me five minutes.I'll go to the business center and print the graphs directly from the spreadsheets.
快去 再给我拿些纸巾
Run.And bring me some paper towels.
怎么了?
What?
我头疼
Oh,I t hurts.
别告诉我你也喝酒了
Don't tell me you were   drinking too.
没有
No!
我的耳朵 我的天!
My ears.Oh,my god!
27岁女性 强烈间歇性耳痛 看过6个医生
27-year-old female,I ntense,I ntermittent ear pain,saw six doctors--
教她别老挤进第一排
tell her to stop lurking in the front row.
如果想勾搭音乐家 去乘巡回表演巴士吧 下一个
If she wants to hit on musicians,that's what tour buses are for.Next.
如果我问为什么我们会在Wilson的办公室 有机会得到直接的答案吗?
If I ask why we're in wilson's office,I s there any chance I'll get a straight answer?
试试看!试试看!
Try it! Try it!
14岁男孩 关节痛和过度体毛生长
14-year-old boy,joint pain and excess hair growth.
告诉他每天手淫不超过三次
Tell him to masturbate no more than three times daily.
饭后进行 下一个
With meals.Next.
我有没有提到那个27岁女性真的很辣?
Did I mention   that the 27-year-old female  is really hot?
但她的丈夫真的不能看
And her husband   is really not.
瞎猜一下 他很有钱
Wild guess,he's rich.
除非社工也开始赚大钱了
Not unless social workers have begun pulling in the big money recently.
给我
Gimme...
你接这个病例是因为她很辣?
You're taking the case because she's hot?
不 那是基因造成的意外
No,that would be an accident of genetics.
是因为她很辣还有她丈夫很丑
It's because she's hot and her husband is ugly.
这是个可以窥探人类心理秘密的神奇窗口
It's a fascinating window into the mysteries of human psychology.
当然还有 她真的很辣
Also,she's really hot.
或者... 她 你知道 爱她的丈夫
Or...  She,you know,loves her husband.
她爱他的某些方面
She loves something about him.
维生素缺乏 她几个月前改变了她的饮食
Vitamin deficiency?She changed her diet a few months ago.
变得更健康了
To a healthier diet.
粗粮 许多坚果
Raw foods,lots of nuts.
不是耳朵 是心脏
It's not the ear,I t's the heart.
她的蛋白质摄取是奶酪 那会提高胆固醇 她的已经很高了
Her protein is cheese,which can raise cholesterol.Hers was already elevated.
造成了动脉阻塞
Gave her arterial blockages.
心率不齐表现为耳痛 很罕见 酷
Cardiac arrhythmia presenting as ear pain.Very rare.Cool.
美女与野兽 谁想去看
So beauty and the beast.Who wants to go see?
Wibberly来电
***
我看看-- Taub Foreman Chase还有Hadley医生
Let's see--dr. Taub,foreman,chase,and hadley.
- 四个都来了 - 难以置信我有这么多医生
- Four for four. - Wow,I  can't believe I get all these doctors.
有的还这么好看
And such good-looking ones too.
是的 看起来简直有点多余
Yeah.It's almost like we don't all need to be here.
你的病提供了一个很有意义诊断学问题
Your case presented a very interesting diagnostic challenge.
你不能睡在你自己的办公室里? 或者卧室吗?
You can't sleep in your own office?Or bedroom for that matter?
必须避开我自然栖息地
Got to avoid my natural habitat.
有个跟我一起上医学院的白痴不停发短信 来说想过来吃午饭
Some idiot I went to med school with keeps leaving messages and wants to drop by for lunch.
- 拒绝他 - 这很复杂
- So tell him no. - It's complicated.
对你而言 告诉某人你不想应酬很复杂吗?
It's too complicated   for you  to tell someone you don't like to screw off?
那简直可说是你的爱好
That's practically   your hobby.
几个月前他是... 我疗程的一部分
A few months ago he was... Sort of part of my therapy.
我的心理医生让我写一封道歉信 给一个我伤害过的人
My shrink told me  to write a letter of apology to someone I hurt.
你怎么伤害他的?
And how did you hurt him?
我们在同一个扁形虫遗传学的研究班课程 我把我俩的期末论文调换了
We were in a seminar on flatworm genetics.I switched my final paper with his.
你作弊了? 不像你啊
You plagiarized?Doesn't sound like you.
我在试验一个理论 我认为那个教授对我有成见
I was testing a theory.I thought that our professor was biased against me.
我认为他用我的论文会拿个高分 我用他的会拿个低分
I assumed he'd get a high grade with my paper and I'd get a low grade with his.
有趣的是 我错了 我得了个"A"
Interestingly,I  was wrong.I got an "a".
所以你在精神病院 钻研你的潜意识
So you're in this mental hospital,delving into your subconscious,
你选择道歉的对象就是这个人?
and this is who you choose to apologize to?
是滴 Lorenzo Wibberly
Yep.Lorenzo wibberly.
在这个世界上你所有伤害过的人之中
Of all the people in the world you've hurt?
不是每个人的名字都那么容易在白页上找到
Not everyone has a name  that's so easy to find in the white pages.
...有我 还有Cuddy
Um...I'm in there,and so is cuddy.
是的 但我选择了他 很奇怪 是吗?
Yeah.And yet,I  picked him.It's funny,I sn't it?
是的 太有趣了 很高兴见到你的治疗收效甚高
Yes,I t's hilarious.Great to see what a success your therapy was.
我们说过生气不过夜的
We said we'd never go to sleep angry.
我们确实发现了心率不齐 但不是来自你的动脉 那儿很正常
We did find an arrhythmia.But it's not from your arteries.They're clean.
会再疼吗?
Will the pain come back?
我们会给她心脏病药 那会有帮助的
We'll start her on cardiac meds.That should help.
但我们还是需要找出是什么导致了心率不齐
But we still need to figure out what's causing the arrhythmia.
嗨 Valerie
Hey,valerie.
Russ
Russ.
你能过来真好
It's so nice of you to stop by.
我现在有很多时间了
I got lots of free time now.
你不是怪我吧?
You don't blame me,do you?
你在Norris面前喝醉了
You were drunk in front of norris.
不 不…
No.No,no,no,no,no.
我现在喝醉了
I'm drunk now.
当时 我像是被人下毒了
Then,I t was like someone poisoned me or something.
你过些时候再来吧
Maybe you should come back later.
好的
Okay.
我只是想说声再见
I just wanna say good-bye.
好的 Russ 谢谢你过来探我
Okay,russ.Thank you for coming by.
你干什么?
What are you doing?
你这可怜的狗杂种 她爱你还不如爱我多
You poor son of a bitch.She doesn't love you any more than she loved me.
好了 你必须马上离开
Okay,you need to leave right now.
你想假装和我妻子有外遇?
You're pretending you had an affair with my wife?
是的 我们都在装 你什么都不用担心
Yeah,we're all pretending.You got nothing to worry about.
告诉他你六个月前在哪里 Russ
Tell him where you were six months ago,russ.
我崩溃了
I had a breakdown.
我有妄想狂倾向 像他们所说的
I had some paranoid tendencies,as they say.
但事实证明 我有理由得妄想狂
But it turns out,I  had a right to be paranoid.
你需要帮助
You need help.
把他弄出去
Get him out of here.
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
我的天
Oh,my god.
- 亲爱的 你还好吗? - 是的 我还好
- Honey,are you okay? - Yeah,I 'm okay.
我们会盯着的 他不会再回来了
We'll keep an eye out.He's not getting back into the hospital.
这些都是他编出来的 你知道对吗?
He's making all that up.You know that,right?
是的 当然
Yeah,of course.
- 你在那里? - 不可泄露地点
- Where are you? - Undisclosed location.
你在躲谁?
Who are you hiding from?
Wilson
Wilson.
还有那个午餐约会 Wilson肯定在努力促成
And the lunch date that wilson is,no doubt,right now trying to sic on me.
但在我们这场伟大的棋局似的关系中
But in the great game of chess that is our relationship,
Wilson只能看到下一步 我却能看到下几十步
wilson sees only one move ahead.I see dozens.
那也是为什么他永远配不上我
That is why   he will never mate me.
这是象棋词汇
That's a chess term.
好极了 一名同事当面对质我们的病人
That's great.A co-worker confronted our patient.
精神不稳定 指责她对他下毒
Altered mental status.Basically accused her of poisoning him.
我们认为他把自己投射到她身上
We think he was projecting.
所以是他对她下毒
So he's poisoning her.
他能弄到什么药物导致室上性心跳过速?
What could he get his hands on to cause supraventricular tachycardia?
他皮肤干燥吗? 眉毛稀疏?
Does he have dry skin?Thin eyebrows?
如果你们正瞠目结舌 请大声一点
If you're sharing an amazed look,please do it louder.
- 好像是有 - 你怎么知道的?
- he might have. - How did you know that?
如果他有甲状腺功能减退 而他把他的药放在她的咖啡里
If he has hypothyroidism and he dumped his meds in her coffee,
那会让她的心脏狂跳 往死里跳
that would make her heart go boom.In a bad way.
我们给她用β-受体阻滞药
We'll treat with beta blockers.
对不起 但我完全不同意
I'm sorry,but I totally disagree.
- 不同意什么? - 所有一切
- With what? - With everything.
为什么我们假设他在说谎而她在讲真话?
Why are we assuming he's lying and she's telling the truth?
因为她很个成功的 婚姻幸福的高级顾问
Because she's a successful,happily married consultant,
而他是个疯疯颠颠 醉醺醺的古怪人 我们刚才把他赶出了医院
and he's a crazy,drunk weirdo who we just tossed out of the hospital.
- 而且她很辣 - 也许就是因为他脆弱她才选择他
- And she's hot. - Maybe she picked him   because he's vulnerable.
她一定有问题 我能感觉到
There's something off about her,I  can feel it.
如果你有任何证据 那就--
If you had any evidence,I t would be--
为什么她没告诉我们 就在她发作前 一个同事呕吐在她的鞋上?
why didn't she tell us a co-worker puked on her shoes right before she collapsed?
因为这和医学无关 他喝醉了 她病了
Because it's medically irrelevant.He was drunk,she was sick.
你不觉得她连她丈夫也没告诉 这点很可疑吗?
You don't think   it's suspicious   she didn't even   mention it to her husband?
Foreman 你为什么和13分手?
Yeah,foreman.Why did you break up with thirteen?
不 等等 她说得这么直白 干嘛?
Oh,no,wait,the non-subtextual thing she was saying,why that?
我们在讨论病例 可不是你在幻想的 我和Foreman之间的事
This is about the case,not some imaginary issue that you think foreman and I have.
很好 给她服用β阻断剂
Great,start her on beta blockers.
你去吧?
You'll do it?
我可不觉得他是对我说的
I don't think he was talking to me.
但我在对你说
Well,I  am.
这里就我认为你是错的
I'm the only one who thinks you're wrong.
也许这正是我让你负责此事的原因
Maybe that's why I'm asking you to do it.
你是Greg吧?
Greg?
我是Lorenzo Wibberly.
Lorenzo wibberly.
Wilson医生说你在这 你还好吗?
Dr. Wilson said you'd be here.How ya been?
将杀
Check and mate.
听着...也许我来这儿会有点尴尬
Look... I'm sorry this is awkward or whatever.
但我只是觉得 你能写那封信真是太好了
I just thought it was nice of you to write that letter,
我想告诉你 你不必觉得内疚
and I wanted to tell you that you don't have to feel bad.
谢谢
Thanks.
你现在在哪工作?
So where are you working these days?
是自己开了诊所还是在医院工作?
You got your own practice or you at a hospital?
我还以为你知道呢
I thought you knew.
我在DanI's工作 是一家有机食品连锁超市
DanI's,the organic supermarket chain.
作为驻店医生?
As an in house doctor?
其实我根本没拿到行医执照
I actually never got licensed.
我没能从医学院毕业
I didn't graduate med school.
我曾想过回学校重读 但我父亲病了
I planned on going back,and then my father got sick
我得照顾他 运气欠佳
and I had to  take care of him  and had some bad luck.
你怎么会没毕业的?
Why didn't you graduate?
我挂了一门课 当时也已经被留校察看了 所以...
I was one credit short.And I was sort of already on academic probation.So...
哪门课?
Which credit?
我... 就是你换了我论文的那门挂了
I got a,um... He failed me on that paper you switched.
我还以为你知道的
I thought you knew.
我猜你是这个连锁超市的CEO吧?
So I'm guessing you're the ceo of this supermarket chain?
我负责给食物装袋
I bag groceries.
人生有时就是这么不可思议
Life works out weird sometimes.
因为他父母的缘故 我们本来是打算在圣巴巴拉市结婚的
We were gonna do it in santa barbara because of his parents.
但后来我在蒙塔克 找到了一家很美的旅馆 所以...
But then I found this beautiful hotel in montauk and--
你在检查她是不是有脑瘤?
you're testing her  for a brain tumor?
这只不过是我的说辞而已 你看过检测仪之后再怪我也不迟
That's what I told her.You can chastise me after you look at the monitor.
看看哪块区域变亮了
Look what's   lighting up.
侧额叶 布若卡氏区 怎么了?
Lateral frontal cortex.Broca's area--so what?
我告诉她 做核磁共振时 常常通过说话来放松
I told her it was customary to talk during mris,to relax.
这半小时内我一直在问她喜欢什么
I spent the last 30 minutes   asking her about   everything in life   that she loves,
讨厌什么 随便什么感情有波动的事
then hates,then feels any emotion about at all.
缘叶旁系统 杏仁核没有反应
There's nothing in the paralimbic system,amygdala.
因为她使用的是大脑的语言区域 绕过了情感区
Because she's using the language part of her brain and bypassing the emotional.
她可以理解喜爱 痛苦和同情 但她完全感受不到
She can understand   love and pain and empathy,but she can't feel them at all.
她精神变态
She's a psychopath.
你为什么那么想见她?
Why do you want to meet her so badly?
精神病患者一直很能吸引我
Psychopaths always fascinate me.
我觉得是因为他们注重文化传承 而且有强烈的家庭观
I think it's their cultural literacy and strong family values.
要么那是犹太人?
Or is that jews?
要是想不到办法让她丈夫离开 我们没法解读真实的她
We're not gonna be able to get an honest read on her unless we figure out a way to get the husband out of there.
我有办法
I got an idea.
你能出去吗?
Can you get out of here?
谢谢
Thanks.
起作用的是那句"谢谢"
It was the "thanks" that did it.
嗨 我是House医生
Hi,I 'm dr. House.
你患精神病多久了?
How long have you been a psychopath?
- 你在开玩笑吧? - 他没有
- Are you kidding? - He's not.
你是说我是Ted Bundy这种人吗? (连环杀人犯 患有精神疾病)
Are you saying I'm like ted bundy or something?
精神变态的名声不太好
Psychopathy  can get a bad rap.
但这并不代表你有暴力倾向
It doesn't necessarily mean you're violent.
你只不过完全没有善恶观 缺乏正常的感情
Just that you're completely without conscience,you lack any normal emotion,
操纵身边的人 滥交 病理性地说谎
you manipulate everyone around you,you're promiscuous,you lie pathologically.
和你像吗?
Any of this ringing bells?
这是你问我那些奇怪问题的原因吗?
Is that why you were asking me all those weird questions?
对 不过你得感谢达尔文
Yeah--though you have darwin to thank for that.
她跟你接触觉得惊慌
She got the creeps around you.
奇怪的是 这确是精神变态者 在周遭会引发的医学现象
Which oddly,I s an actual medical phenomenon around psychopaths.
也许是弱者进化出对掠食者的本能反应
Probably an evolved response   to predators.
抱歉 你真的吓到我了 我完全不明白...
I'm sorry,you're really freaking me out.I have no idea what--
放松点 我们有义务替你保密
relax.We have a duty of confidentiality.
你还有个尚未查明的心脏问题 很可能会随时害死你
And you have an undiagnosed heart problem that could kill you at any moment.
我们认为你的精神异常 和生理病症有关
We believe that your mental abnormality is related to your physical one.
所以 如果你想继续掠食
So if you want to keep on predating...
你想知道什么?
What do you want to know?
你同事说的是真的 你下毒害他
Your co-worker's story was true.You poisoned him.
不是 我给他服了点安定和催吐剂
No.I gave him a little valium and an emetic.
你真明白"不是"这个词的含义吗?
You sure you understand what the word "no" means?
- 我以前就同时吃过 他为什么不能? - 这么说你是在帮他了?
- I've had them both before,why can't he? - So you were just helping him out?
我猜他对被色诱 被炒鱿鱼的事都不在乎?
And I assume he was cool with the whole seducing and firing part too?
Russ很清楚利益交换
Russ knew what he was getting into.
他每周四晚都能和我上床 而他的好创意归我
He got sex every thursday night,and I got to take credit for his best ideas.
你能从婚姻得到什么好处?
And what are you getting out of your marriage?
和你从工作中得到的一样
Same thing you get out of your job.
Bill有个信托基金
Bill has a trust fund.
他父母逼我签了婚前协议
And I have a prenup his parents made me sign.
都说他有钱了 她没那么奇怪
Told you he was rich.She's not that weird.
我和别人没太大区别
I'm not so different than anybody else.
我所认识的所有人 家人 同学 同事...
Everyone I've ever known-- my family,my classmates,the people I work with--
他们都是为了自己 区别在于 我肯承认这点
they're all out for themselves.Difference is,I  could admit it to myself.
她有点让我想起了某人
She kind of reminds me of someone I know.
还用你说
Tell me about it.
我的一些同事还会当面羞辱人
Some of my co-workers will insult people right to their faces.
你这样多久了?
How long have you been this way?
我从来如此
Just how I am.
你现在肯治疗我的心脏问题了吗?
Are you gonna cure my heart problems now?
精神变态加上心率不齐 说吧
So psychopathy plus cardiac arrhythmia.Go.
我还以为你恐吓是想套话呢 你真觉得两者有关系?
I thought you were bluffing to get information.You really think they're connected?
病人同时有两个罕见的病症 这么假设很正常
Two rare conditions in one patient,I t's a fair assumption they are.
神经病通常都是遗传性的 对此我们也无能为力
Psychopathy is generally just genetic.Nothing you can do about it.
出生三十年后突发的问题 两者不会有关系的
Something that hits 30 years after birth isn't gonna be connected.
她的病可没法潜伏那么久
Her disease isn't gonna lie dormant that long.
会不会是心脏导致大脑异常?
Did her heart warp her brain?
- 有许多病症都能 - 我们要是能找出来 那一定很酷
- Maybe a handful of diseases. - It'll be super awesome when we find it.
三期梅毒会导致 伪精神病并发症和心肌炎
Tertiary syphilis can cause pseudopsychopathic syndrome  and cardiomyopathy.
很合理 给她用盘尼西林 排除威尔森氏症和桥本病
Fits best.Start her on penicillin,and rule out wilson's and hashimoto's.
这就是你说的一堆病 也不是很难诊断 对吧?
There's your handful.Wasn't so hard,was it?
你得约束一下13 她藐视你我的权威
You've gotta do something about thirteen.She flouted both my authority and yours.
对 但她是对的 你是错的
Yes,and she got it right and you got it wrong.
这只会教情况恶化 她还会故技重施的
Which just aggravates the problem.She'll do it again.
下次可就没这么好运了
Next time it won't work out so well.
你得处罚她
You gotta punish her.
你才是她的上司
You're her boss.
在某种含糊无效的定义下 得由你处罚她
In some vague,never to be usefully defined way.You punish her.
我也是她的前男友 你知道的 这把事情搞得有点复杂了
I'm also her ex,which,as you know,makes it a little complicated.
你炒了她的事更让事态 从有点复杂变成了有点白痴
The fact that you also fired her takes it from a little complicated to a little moronic.
- 只有这样我才能... - 这并不是因为你太爱她
- It was the only way I could-- it wasn't because you were too in love with her.
而是因为你太爱你的事业了
It was because you were too in love with your career.
快到我这层了 我总结一下
We're almost at my floor so I'll summarize.
这是你的问题 不是我的
Your problem,not mine.
你剪坏了的照片 我只有一张
You cut up my only copy of that photo.
那张用银版法拍摄的罕见相片
That rare daguerreotype.
你从硬盘再影印一张耗费的气力 算我账上
You can charge me for the effort it takes to search your hard drive for a new copy.
我不是说和Lucas的那张合照
Not the one of me and lucas.
是厄瓜多尔的那张
The one from ecuador.
没错 我忘记你对狐猴的深厚感情了
Right.I had forgotten your deep emotional attachment to lemurs.
是对我的爸爸
To my dad.
- 你遗传了他的尾巴? - 照片是他拍的
- You got his tail. - He was holding the camera.
那是我们最后一次共同旅行
That was the last trip we ever took together.
而且我没有数码的副本
And I don't have a digital copy.
我可以花整天时间站在这道歉 但我宁愿用心工作来赎罪
Well,I  could stand here all day apologizing,but I'd rather expiate my sins with good clean work.
你无视我的短信?
You ignoring my texts?
你是指那些你毁了同窗的一生 指望我让你感觉好受些的短信?
The crazy ones you sent trying to get me to make you feel better about destroying your classmate's life?
没 我没收到
No,I  never got those.
他是谁?
Y este quién es?
是个医师
Él es un doctor de medición
还是个医生
Wilson医生叫我来会诊 Wibberly有企图
Dr. Wilson...  Wibberly's got some agenda.
也许是想让我感到内疚 好让我给他找一个好工作
Probably trying to guilt me into getting him a better job.
- 他有多生气? - 完全不生气
- How pissed was he? - Not at all.
所以我才知道他有所企图
That's how I know he's got an agenda.
好痛
Me duele mucho
那你就不该敲上去
Entonces no te lo hubieras golpeado
我的工作环境很危险
Trabajo en condiciones muy peligrosas
如果你觉得内疚就该帮帮他
If you feel guilty,you should do something to help.
这的确是你的责任
You are responsible.
别担心 Wilson医生是个很好的医师
No te preocupes.  El Dr. Wilson es un muy buen médico.
谢谢
Thanks.
他对自身性功能障碍的抗争
Who has enormous empathy towards patients
使得他对病人移情甚深
which stems from his own crippling battle with male sexual dysfunction.
什么?
What?
我只需对换论文的可预见性结果负责
All I'm responsible for is the foreseeable consequences of switching papers.
差一些的成绩或者一个不眠之夜 最多就是补考
A bad grade or a sleepless night,worst case,a retest.
我怎么知道一份期末论文 会毁了这个白痴的一生
There was no way to know that one seminar paper was gonna destroy this idiot's life.
如果有因果报应的话 或许他比你快乐
If there's any karma  n all this,he's probably happier than you are.
有道理
Good point.
如果他更高兴了 那我就没造成什么伤害 我去查查看
If he's happier,there's no harm done.I'll go find out.
我可不是这意思
That is absolutely not what I said.
这家伙一直很谦虚
Always with the modesty,this one.
下次还想在工作时嗑药
Next time you want to get secretly stoned at work
错把拇指当成钉子吗? 眼药水这招不错
and mistake your thumb for a nail?  Eyedrops are a good call,
不过别用得太多 你这么频繁掉眼泪就是由此引起的
but use less,  that's why you're tearing up so much.
他说什...
What did--
他说你是个很好的医生
He says you are a very good doctor.
你想吃点什么吗?
you want something to eat?
不必了
I'm cool.
工作如何?
How's work?
你喜欢吗?
You happy with it?
你明白的... 就是份工作而已
You know... It's a job.
至少我不用带工作回家
I don't need to take any work home with me at least.
空暇时间... 如果你是医生的话就没有了
Free time... Wouldn't have any of that if you were a doctor.
对 没错
Yeah.True.
你喜欢辣椒吗? 我可以给你重新加热一点
You like chili?I could reheat some.
这是你的院子吗?
Is that your yard?
挺不错的
That's nice.
对
Yeah.
那棵糖枫树有100... 150岁了
That sugar maple,100,150 years old.
在秋天叶子可漂亮了
Most beautiful leaves in the fall.
坐在底下的长凳上... 感觉就像身处天堂
Sitting underneath on the bench-- it's like paradise.
我没有院子
I don't have a yard,myself.
你过得不错
You got a good thing going.
- 我知道 - 这些盒子是干什么用的?
- I know. - So what are the boxes for?
我要搬家了
I'm moving.
离开天堂?
From paradise?
我父亲的医药费 加上我是个白痴 签了可调利率的抵押贷款
Well,my dad's medical bills and me being one of those idiots that got an adjustable mortgage.
- 所以... - 你的房子要被收走了?
- So... - You're losing your home?
嘿 事情可能会更糟的 对吧?
Hey,I t could be worse,right?
怎么可能?
How?
即便测试结果呈阳性 你也不必担心
Even if the tests are positive,you don't have to worry.
- 你测试的是梅毒 可不是感冒 - 宝贝...
- You're testing for syphilis,not a cold. - Honey...
对这个阶段来说 可能并不会传染
At this stage,I t's probably   not communicable.
你觉得我是在担心自己? 我只希望我太太能好起来
You think I'm worried about myself?I just want my wife   to get better.
她也许在出生时就患上了 这并不能证明她在外偷情
She might have caught it at birth.So it doesn't prove she was cheating.
- 如果担心这点的话 - 当然不
- If you were worried about that. - Of course not.
我得在这待几周...
How many weeks am I gonna have to--
还好吗? 她为什么在咳嗽?
you okay?Why    she coughing?
我不知道 你想喝水吗?
I don't know.Do you want some water?
你感觉到我威胁你吗?
Are you threatened by me?
完全没有
Not at all.
你应该有这感觉
Well,you should be.
如果你向他告密 我不仅要让你执照报销
You let him know what I told you,I  will not only have your license pulled,
我离婚失去的一切 都会从你身上讨回来
i will sue you for everything I lose in the divorce.
揭发我得到的乐趣 值得1900万美元吗?
So the fun you get out of making those snotty little comments,I s it worth $19 million?
慢 保持这个表情
Oh,wait,will you hold that look?
我不擅长表露情绪 你看这个如何?
I'm really bad at showing emotions.How's this?
谢了 宝贝
Thanks,baby.
手臂伸给我好吗?
Can I have your arm please?
我的手臂! 你把它拗断了!
My arm!You broke it!
我不知道这怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
我也不知道 但我知道结果
Neither do i,but I know what happened after.
她打给Cuddy 要把你踢出这病例
She called cuddy and demanded that I kick you off the case.
我替你说话了 因为我信得过你
I backed you up,because I trust you.
你得好好表现 别辜负我
But you're gonna have to earn that trust now.
谢谢
Thanks.
实际上 他替你说话 是因为新的血尿素氮和肌酐指数
Actually,he backed you up because of the new b.U.N.Creatinine numbers.
骨质脆弱是肾脏衰竭导致
Brittle bones were from kidney failure.
- 被揭穿了 那么说 心脏加肾脏 - 还有脑子
- There is that.So heart and kidneys. - And brain.
- 不 精神变态不是症状 - 你昨天还说是
- Nope.Psychopathy is not a symptom. - It was yesterday.
但肾衰竭排除了梅毒 检查排除了其它与此相关的诊断
In the meantime,kidney failure ruled out syphilis and testing ruled out the other ideas that would've fit.
蛋白质水平 肾脏 心律不齐
Protein levels,kidneys,arrhythmia.
可能是副肿瘤综合症 我说是淋巴癌
Could be paraneoplastic.I'd say lymphoma.
给她上放射性疗法
Get her to radiotherapy.
在做尿液免疫测定前 不能开始放射性治疗
We can't start radiation without immunoassays on her urine.
那好 你施法把她的肾治好 我们好取尿液做检查
Great,so you cast a spell and magically fix her kidney  so she can give us   some urine to test.
- 她入院时取的还有剩 - 量太少 结果不够准确
- We have some left over from admission. - Not enough for a completely accurate reading.
部分准确也好啊
Then how about partially accurate?
那些没有一起睡过的人 可以离场了
Those of you who haven't slept together,you can go.
其他人留下
Everyone else,stay behind.
对不起
Sorry.
这是我们的秘密
That was our secret,right?
- 开房去吧 - 不用 谢谢
- Go have sex. - No,thanks.
好吧 伟哥和润滑剂算我的 把收据给我就好
Fine,I 'll cover the viagra and the lubricants.Just get me a receipt.
我们之间毫无感觉了
We have zero feelings for each other.
杯具了 因为你们睡在一起时 情况比现在好得多
Well,that's too bad,'cause things worked much better when you did.
如果我和她上床会有帮助吗?
Would it help if I slept with her?
- 我们在进行诊断 - 不 我们已经得出了诊断
- We were getting to a diagnosis. - No,we were already at the diagnosis.
你们为一个不相干的检查争论不休 因为你们无法忍受对方
***'Cause you can't stand to be around each other.
要么上床 要么干一架 要么走人 随便你们
So have sex,fight or quit,I  don't care.
反正这样下去行不通
Whatever you're doing now isn't working.
你没事吧?
You okay?
没事
Yeah.
我知道治疗很紧急 但放疗?
Look,I  get that you gotta act fast-- radiation?
你们彻底排除了其它可能性?
You definitely ruled out everything else?
对不起 但...
I'm sorry,but...
我们还可以检查环境毒素
We could still check for environmental toxins.
她多数时间待在哪里?
Where does she spend most of her time?
- 大部分时间在工作 家里 - 爱好?
- Mostly at work,at home-- hobbies?
经常进行室外活动?
Recurring activities outside the home?
没有 她参加了一个园艺班
No,not really.She took a landscaping class.
在基督教青年会
At the y.
他们什么时候上课?
When did it meet?
这个夏天每周四晚上
Every thursday night this summer.
你挖掘泥土时 可能会接触 杀虫剂 重金属等有害物质
You dig in soil,you can be exposed to pesticides,heavy metals,lots of bad things.
你能查出她上课的 具体地点等细节吗?
Can you find out all about her landscaping class,where it was,details like that?
好 我现在就去
Yeah,I 'll do it now.
你看星球大战时支持哪一边?
So when you watch  star wars,which side do you root for?
House医生
Dr. House.
你想干什么?
What are you doing?
观察你的放射性治疗
Just checking in on your radiotherapy.
据我所知 你从不探访病人
From what I hear,you never visit patients.
但迄今你已经找我谈了两次
And now,you've come to chat with me twice.
我想问问你 做管理顾问感觉如何?
I want to know how you like being a management consultant.
我在考虑转行
I'm thinking of getting into it.
做这个 或全职心理变态
That or psychopathy,maybe.
哪个比较好赚?
Which pays better?
我想你已是其中之一了
I think you're already into one of them.
Hadley医生昨天开玩笑说 我听起来就像是你
Dr. Hadley   made a joke yesterday.She said I sound like you.
我肯定你理解"玩笑"的意思
I'm sure you understand what joke means.
难道你做的一切不是为自己?
So you're not just   out for yourself?
比方说 你不会为满足一己好奇 而干扰一个病重女人的治疗?
For example,you would never interrupt a sick woman's treatment just because of some personal obsession?
没错 我很自私自利 我们都这样 天性如此
Of course I'm self-interested.We all are.We're born that way.
但我们天性里也有良知
The rest of us are born with consciences.
你似乎为此感到很欣喜
Which is something  you just sound ecstatic about.
我不是说这合乎情理 但无可否认是人类本性
I'm not saying it's logical.I'm just saying it's human.
如果你知道你的良知不过是动物本能 就不必受约束了
So if you know your conscience is just an animal instinct,you don't need to follow it.
你想必深知这一点
I think you realize that.
否则也不会和我谈
That's why   you're talking to me.
园艺课是你编出来的
You lied about your landscaping class.
Hadley医生认为 土壤里可能有毒素
Dr. Hadley thought the soils might be poisoned.
你告诉他了?
You told him that?
- 我只是-- - Russ说你们有一腿
- I just thought--  russ said you were having an affair.
这就是你的掩饰?
Was that your cover?
每个星期四晚上 你--
Every thursday night   you'd--
- 对不起 - 天啊
-  I'm so sorry. - Oh,god.
事情不是你想的那样
It's not   what you think.
记得我告诉过你 去年失去一个电信案子吗?
Do you remember that telecom case I said that we didn't get last year?
其实我们谈拢了 我为这事忙坏了
In fact,we did,and I was swamped.
每周五早上我都要 和伦敦那边开电话会议
Every friday morning we had a conference call with london,
- 所以前一天晚上-- - 这是你的借口?
- so the night before I would--  that's   your excuse?
你以为我会相信你在办公室?
You expect me to believe that you were at the office?
我们吵过最激烈是哪一次?
What's the biggest argument we've ever had?
你说我花太多时间在外面
You said   I spend too much time  away from home.
你说我根本不需要工作 你会照顾我
That I don't need a job,that you would take care of me.
我是发自内心的
Yeah,that's all true.
你朝我大嚷了
You yelled at me.
你让我觉得 你不尊重我做的一切
You made me feel like you didn't value anything that I did.
我需要这份工作 让我觉得自己有所成就
I need this job  to feel like I'm accomplishing something on my own.
所以我才会向你撒谎
That's why I lied to you.
如果我明天打到你办公室 发现--
If I call your office tomorrow and I check--
尽管打给我办公室 我秘书 我的客户--
call my office,call my secretary,call my clients--
打断他们的晚餐 把他们吵醒好了 我不在乎
interrupt their dinner,wake them up,I  don't care.
我只想你知道真相
I just want you to know the truth.
你知道的 我爱你
You know I love you.
过来
Come here.
求你了
Please.
没事的
It's okay.
开除她
Fire her.
为什么? 你的如簧巧舌已经让你开脱了
What for?You seemed to have lied your way out of any trouble.
如果Bill调查一下就露馅了
Until bill checks up on my cover.
我又得编另一个谎话来掩盖这一个
And I have to create a whole new one to cover that one up.
虽然我曾经这样做 但很难受
I've done it before but it's a pain.
Hadley医生让我难受 我也不会让她好过
And I would like dr. Hadley to share that pain.
她没有泄露任何病人隐私
She didn't reveal any confidences,
她有正当的医学理由 去查问你园艺班的事
and she had a valid medical reason to ask about your landscaping class.
我们姑且看陪审团怎么说
We can see what a jury says about that.
还可以看你如何向丈夫坦白? 你不会告我们的
And admit to your husband the truth?You're not gonna sue us.
- 我们将中止Hadley医生和病人接触 - 什么?
- We will remove dr. Hadley from all patient contact. - What?
但这是为了Hadley医生的利益着想 而不是为了你
But it's for dr. Hadley's benefit,not yours.
- 我们没义务打压她来迁就你 - 那好
- **** - Fine.
但不妨告诉你 这不是为你着想
But just so you know,this is not for your benefit.
Cuddy医生很光火 你差点让医院吃官司
Dr. Cuddy's furious that you put her hospital at risk.
但她不想在我面前承认
She just knows   it's a bad idea to admit it   in front of me.
随便你怎么想 护工就在外头
Think what you want.By the way,your orderly's outside.
但要是我 会再等10分钟
But I'd wait about another ten minutes
好让你丈夫以为 你在进行放射治疗
if you really want your husband to think you're having radiation treatments.
Hadley医生 你要哭了吗?
Dr. Hadley,are you by chance gonna cry?
我从来都哭不出来
'Cause that's one I just can't do.
喂?
Hello?
我是Hadley医生
This is dr. Hadley.
什么?
What?
你打给医学委员会?
You called the medical board?
你在说什么?
What is she talking about?
投诉我性骚扰 你以为我不知道是你?
Accusations   of sexual harassment.You don't think I know it's you?
13 冷静点
Thirteen,come on.
你已经把我踢出了这病例 你还想怎样?
You already got me fired from the case.What else do you want?
Hadley医生
Dr. Hadley.
马上出来
Get out here now.
- 你的行为简直愚不可及 - 她想害我丢执照!
- You're acting like an idiot. - She's trying to make me lose my license.
她办不到 除非你蠢得 跑到她房间去大喊大叫
And she'll fail,unless you're stupid enough  to go in there   and scream at her.
性骚扰是非常严重的投诉
Sexual harassment accusations are incredibly serious.
如果她匿名投诉 这案子铁定会销掉
If she made them anonymously,the case goes away.
如果她具名投诉 有我们给你作证 还是会销掉
If she used her name,we all back you up,I t goes away.
你反应过激了
You're completely overreacting.
换作是你也没法忍
You'd be pissed off too if you were me.
也许不会 谁知道呢 你和她一样冷酷无情
Or maybe not,I  don't know.You're just about as emotional as she is.
- 我这是在帮你 - 我知道
- I'm doing you a favor. - I know.
即便你是在做好事 听起来也像个混蛋
And even when you try to do something nice,you sound like a jerk.
对不起
I'm sorry.
为什么?
For what?
我把你开除了
For firing you.
别说这个 两件事根本不相干
Don't do that,that's not what this is about.
我还是要道歉
Then I'll   apologize anyway.
我这么做是为了我 不是为你
I did it for me.Not for you.
刚把你开除 我就意识到这点了
I realized that right after I fired you.
但我没有勇气承认
But I couldn't admit it.
把一切都搞砸了
Screwed everything up.
我希望我们还能一起工作
I hope that we can still work together.
她的肝出问题了
something's wrong with her liver.
血液倒流 涌入食道
Blood flow is backing up,spilling into her esophagus.
- 因为癌症? - 这不是淋巴癌
- from the cancer? - This isn't lymphoma.
我们不知道病因
We don't know what it is.
我们可以给血管止血 但出血太严重 可能不管用
*******That might not work.
我要采用叫"Tips"的疗法 使血液绕过肝脏的分流术
I want to try something called a "tips," a shunt that makes the blood bypass the liver.
这--可以救她?
That--that'll save her?
可以保住她的肝脏和心脏
It should help preserve her liver and heart.
肝脏将毒素清出 分流时间长了 可能会造成脑损伤甚至生命危险
The liver cleans out toxins,bypass it too long,she'll get brain damage,eventually die.
但也许还是好过流血不止
That's still probably less dangerous than bleeding out now.
也许?
Probably?
一向是Valerie作决定
Valerie usually makes the decisions.
你现在得站出来
You gotta step up now.
她对我不忠吗?
Was she cheating on me?
- 我不能说-- - 就告诉我她是否在撒谎
- I can't discuss-- just tell me she wasn't lying.
告诉我
Just tell me that.
我应该做这个决定?
I'm supposed to make this decision?
我连她是什么人都不知道
I don't even know who she is anymore.
无论如何 你必须马上决定
Either way,you gotta do it right now.
你认为对就去做吧
Do whatever you think is right.
她只能活一天 顶多两天
I'd give her a day.Two days at the most.
太棒了 你负责演时钟
Great.You be the clock.
其他人负责扮医生
Everyone else will be the doctors.
心脏 肾 现在是肝
Heart,kidneys,now liver.
- 淀粉样变性病? - MRI没发现斑点
- Amyloidosis? - No speckles on the mri.
α-1抗胰蛋白酶缺乏症?
Alpha-1 antitrypsin deficiency?
肾衰竭太严重了
Too much kidney failure.
肝纤维化?
Primary hepatic fibrosis?
这是最靠谱的猜测了 给她上类固醇
That's our best guess.Start her on steroids.
即便我们猜对了 肝的损伤太严重
Even if we're right,the liver's probably too scarred.
- 我们得登记给她找个新肝 - 就凭一个不确定的诊断?
- We've got to list her for a new one. - With an unconfirmed diagnosis?
- 不可能获得通过 - 家属捐赠呢?
- Not gonna happen. - How about   a family member?
我想她丈夫血型不一样
I don't think the husband is   the right blood type.
即便吻合 他现在也不愿捐了
Even if he was,he's not gonna give his liver now.
- 他离开她了 我猜? - 还没有
- He left her,I  assume? - not yet.
说是不会在她病重时抛弃她
Says he won't abandon her while she's sick.
她没别的亲人了么?
She have any   other family members?
没人会冒生命危险去救她
No one's gonna risk their life to save hers.
天 一精神病人不过打打你小报告 你就变得如此刻薄了
Man,one false accusation from a psychopath,and you turned out to be a real bummer.
我去看看Wilson还有没肝剩的
I'm gonna go see if wilson has the liver left.
你在干什么?
What are you doing?
替Wibberly还几个月的房贷
Paying wibberly's mortgage for a few months.
恭喜恐吓战术又成功了
Congratulations on another successful round of hectoring.
慢着 这是一张真的支票?
Wait a minute,I s that actually a check for him?
不 这是一张保管中奖的彩票
No.It's a giant novelty item for winning the lottery.
你站太远 瞅不清啊?
You're just standing really far away.
这么多人需要帮助 为何偏偏选这家伙?
Of all the people to go the extra mile for,why this guy?
不知道 大概因为他喷儿香而且总逗我乐
I don't know.He just kinda smells good and makes me laugh.
为什么不是Cuddy? 你还没为剪坏她照片道歉
Why not cuddy?You never apologized after you defaced her photo.
大概因为我觉得把人整得无家可归
Maybe because I recognize that sending someone to the poor house
比篡改照片更严重
is a little more serious than editing a snapshot.
不 因为你对Cuddy有感觉
No,I t's because cuddy actually means something to you,
所以很难开口向她道歉
which makes it much harder to apologize.
唉
Oy.
如果能让你闭嘴 我会为照片的事向她道歉
If it will make you shut up,I  will tell her I'm sorry about the photo.
别提照片的事 House 她这些年一直爱着你
Forget the photo.House,she was in love with you.
换回的却是你的羞辱
And all she got in return was abuse.
这么多年戏弄她的感情
For years you toyed with her emotions.
她才没有爱我
She wasn't in love with me.
你抵死不承认 更加证明了我的观点
The fact that you   **
那你到底想怎样?
***
搭救那家伙是你的主意
helping the guy was your idea.
不 尽管帮他 爱咋咋地...
No,help the guy,whatever...
我只是想指出
I'm just pointing out that it's much easier
通过给一个陌生人砸钱 来摆脱内疚
to soothe your guilt by throwing money at a stranger
比补偿一个你真正在乎的人 要容易得多
than by making amends  to a person you actually cared about.
原来你一直把我当叫花子打发
You had me at "much easier.
我要假装埋头工作了
" I'm gonna pretend to go to work now.
Bing!
Sarah?
我是Hadley医生 抱歉打扰你 听说你是Valerie的姐姐?
I'm dr. Hadley.I'm--I'm sorry to bother you,but I was told you're valerie's sister?
我很意外你会来看她
I was just surprised you came to visit.
我家人也很意外
So istststste of my family.
我更意外的是 你去做捐赠者检查了
I was even more surprised you got tested as a donor.
血型不一致
Wrong blood type.
但为什么? 你明知她是什么人
But why?I mean,you know what she's like.
她其实没那么坏
She's not that bad.
她就这么坏
Yes,she is.
我们父亲是个粗暴的酒鬼
Our dad was a mean drunk.
我是最年长的姐姐
I was the older sister.
我有责任保护她 而不是反过来
I was supposed way around.
她小时候曾保护你?
R she protected you when you were kids?
但突然之间 他的粗暴 他的虐待...
Yeah,and then all of the sudden... All of his crap and all his abuse...
改变了她
It just changed her.
使她变得铁石心肠
It made her cold.
什么时候?
When?
我们搞错了 精神变态是一个症状
We were wrong.Psychopathy is a symptom.
我和她姐姐聊了
I spoke to her sister.
她并非向来如此
She wasn't always like this.
她变了 就在她青春期
She changed,and right around adolescence.
那么说 肝 心脏 脑子 一度潜伏 青春期开始病发
So liver,heart,brain,can lie dormant,and it starts at puberty.
是粗粮食谱导致病发...果仁里富含铜
The raw food diet made it go fulminant... Nuts are high in copper.
是威尔森氏病
It's wilson's disease.
我们已经排除那个了 没有凯-费环
We ruled that out.No keyser-fleischer rings.
还有一个症状
There is one other sign.
我知道有女同性恋用唇膏 (指女同性恋的女生角色)
I know there are lipstick lesbians.
不知道双性恋用不用洗甲水?
Are there nail polish remover bisexuals?
她不该来的
She's not supposed to be here.
作为医生她不能来  你们可没质疑过她作化妆助理的资质
As a doctor.You didn't say anything   about her capacity as a beautician's assistant.
她的指甲是蓝的?
Her fingernail's blue?
是的
Yep.
给她上鏊合剂
Start her on chelation.
刚刚发生了什么?
What just happened?
你会好起来了
You're gonna get better.
你的身体无法代谢铜
Your body has an inability to process copper.
引起了所有问题
It caused all of your problems.
甚至你大脑的问题
Even what's wrong with your brain.
这个也会改善吗?
And that's gonna change too?
也许病症已经永久性改变了她的神经通路
It's probably rewired her neurons permanently by now.
不过还是有可能的?
But it's possible?
有可能
Maybe.
我要去准备鏊合剂治疗的设备
I have to go get the chelation equipment.
Bill 我要你签一些表
Bill,I  need you to sign some forms.
你还不明白她在做什么吗?
You don't see what she's doing?
她在做铺垫 准备好在治疗之后
She's laying the groundwork to get her treatment,
转变成另一个人 这样你和你的钱都还属于她
wake up a completely different person,so that you and all of your money stay with her.
这是个谎言
It's a lie.
你说有可能的
You said there was a chance.
是的 可能性很小
Okay,there's a teeny chance.
但即使治好了她 还是无法让她爱上你
But even if it cures her,I t's not going to make her love you.
我之前很幸福...
I was happy before...
我知道 很抱歉 但这不是真的
I know.And I'm sorry,but it wasn't real.
但感觉很真实
It felt real.
我不知道...
I don't know...
可能那样就足够了
Maybe that can be enough.
你真的要为我这么做?
You're really doing this for me?
能帮我减税的
Tax shelter.
我现在能吃点辣椒了
I'll take some of that chili now.
我不能接受
I can't accept this.
好吧 不吃辣椒了
Fine.Forget the chili.
拜拜 Wibberly
Bye,wibberly.
用你的文章我得了A+
I got an "a"-plus with your paper.
我在纽约Mercy医院做了 十年整形外科医生
I was an orthopedic surgeon for ten years at new york mercy.
我赌博成瘾
I had a gambling problem.
我试图通过多收医保病人的医疗费还赌债 丢了执照
I tried to cover it  by over-billing some medicare patients.Lost my license.
是我沦落至此的原因 不是因为你
That's why I'm here.Not because of you.
为什么你现在告诉我这些?
Why are you telling me this now?
因为我以为你还跟医学院那会儿一样混蛋 但是...
Because I thought you'd be the same bastard you were in med school,but,uh...
拿着
Keep it.
不要 我会找到其它住处的
No,I  can get another place.
拿着 我耍了你
Just take it.I screwed you over.
你让我得了A+
You got me an "a"-plus.
- 拿着 - 不要!
- Take it. - No!
一定要我塞进你喉咙啊?
Do I have to shove it down your throat?
拿着他妈的支票!
Take the damn check!
你的指标好转了
Your vitals are up.
治疗起作用了?
Treatment's working?
我不确定能否治好你的肝脏 但肯定能安排你换个新的
I'm not sure we can fix your liver,but we can  definitely list you for a new one.
等你好一点了 我们去度个长假
When you're better,we're gonna take a long vacation.
你想去越南 在那儿的沙滩 我们可以住在小木屋里
You wanna go to vietnam,one of the beaches,we're gonna get a hut.
只有你和我 什么都不用担心
Just you and me,nothing to worry about.
你真可悲
You're pathetic.
什...什么?
Wha--what?
我是说 之前你还只是怀疑 那还过得去
I mean,when you had a suspicion,fine.
但现在你都已经知道了
But you know now.
你怎么能这么可怜?
How can you be this pitiful?
你不是这个意思
You don't mean this.
- 因为你病了 - 我没有病
- You're sick. - I'm not sick.
我差点死掉 现在仍可能会死
I almost died and I still might.
谁知道呐 可能经此我才下了决心
And who knows,maybe it's focusing my mind
只要一想到要和你过下半辈子 我就...
because the idea of spending the rest of my life with you--
Valerie...
valerie...
你为什么要这么做?
Why did you do that?
因为他很可悲
Because he's pathetic.
他没有变...
He hasn't changed...
是你变了
But you have.
对大脑的治疗真的见效了
The treatment actually worked on your brain.
如果你还有精神变态 你只会继续压榨他
If you were still a psychopath,you would've just kept draining him dry.
- 你想说什么? - 你感觉什么了
- What do you want? - You're feeling something.
是什么?
What is it?
你感觉到什么?
What do you feel?
我不知道
I don't know.
感觉很痛苦
It hurts.
是很痛苦
It will.
听说你的诊断了 干得好
Heard about the diagnosis.Nice job.
谢谢
Thanks.
你这么晚在这儿干什么?
Why are you here so late?
写出院小结
Discharge summary.
Taub的笔迹不太好认
Taub's handwriting isn't helping much.
看起来 入院后第三天 病人开始大量兔子治疗
Apparently on the third day of admission,the patient underwent rabbit thumping.
嗯... 是放疗
Um... Radiotherapy.
入院后第三天 病人开始放疗 包括外放疗...
Third day after admission,patient underwent radiotherapy including external beam radiation...
治疗B细胞性淋巴瘤
To treat b-cell lymphomas.
第一个治疗是...
First treatment was...
全身疗法....
Full mantle therapy...
"why try to change me now" by Fiona Apple
*我多愁善感 所以步入雨中*
*I'm sentimental   so I walk in the rain *
*我有些习惯 自己都无从解释*
*I've got some habits even I can't explain *
*我走向角落*
*i go to the corner *
*留在了西班牙*
*and I end up in spain *
*为什么现在来改变我*
*why try to change me now *
*就让人们遐想*
*so let people wonder *
*让他们欢笑或者忧愁*
*let 'em laugh,let 'em frown *
*为什么要改变我*
*why try to change me *
*为什么你想改变我
*why would you want to change me *
*为什么现在要来改变我*
*why try to change me now *